Guide to the Steven Chu Papers SC0828
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Additional papers, Accession ARCH-2013-061
  - Audiovisual
    - "Lazer Tweezers" Steven Chu (unedited window dub). Tape 1, Undated; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 11)
    - "Lazer Tweezers" Steven Chu (unedited window dub). Tape 2, Undated; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 11)
    - "Lazer Tweezers" Steven Chu (unedited window dub). Tape 3, Undated; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 11)
    - "Lazer Tweezers" Steven Chu (unedited window dub). Tape 4, Undated; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 11)
    - Introduction to the LASER & Experiment, Undated; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 11)
    - RNA Folding Helicase, 1999 Jun 03; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 11)
    - Meliora Overview, 2000/2001; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 11)
    - PS Photos (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Raman Cooling Figures, 1992 (Box 6)
    - What is Music?, Undated; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 11)
    - Visionaries, Undated; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 11)
    - Unlabled (7), Undated; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 11)
    - Chu - 60th, 2008; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD)
    - Chu Personal [Images], Undated (Box 11)
    - LBL Aerials [Images], 2006 (Box 11)
    - Photographs with Bush and Schwarzenegger (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - KQED Forum with Michael Krasny, 2013 Dec 18; 1 computer file(s) (MP3)
    - Lean Lederman Panel, 1999 Oct 11 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - AFOSR Where Ideas Take Flight McLarty Communications, 2000 Sep 8 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Mind and Life X - Day 4: The Nature of Matter, the Nature of Life, 2002 Oct 3 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - 2002 Global Conference: Nobel Laureates in Science and Medicine (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Nobel Prize Awards (in Swedish), 1997 Dec 10 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - University of Rochester Sesquicentennial Celebration, Undated (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Steven Chu "The Dye Laser 25 Years Symposium", 1991 May 10 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Interview with Alan Acosta Stanford News Service, Undated (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Engineer's Club, Dayton, Ohio, 1998 Jan (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Global Conference 2003: Luncheon: Nobel Laureates in Medicine and Science, 2003 Apr 1 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - The Dye Laser - 25 Years Symposium (Tape 1 of 3), 1991 May 10 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - The Dye Laser - 25 Years Symposium (tape 2 of 3), 1991 May 10 (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - The Dye Laser - 25 Years Symposium (Tape 1 of 3), 1991 May 10 (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Celebrate a Century of Physics Nobel Luncheon version, Undated (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Dr. Steven Chu 1997 Nobel Winner News Conference, 1997 Oct 15 (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Nobel Prize (announcement, award, banquet), 1998 Oct 9 (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - Steven Chu 1997 Nobel Prize for Physics, Clip Reel, 1997 Oct 15 (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - Steven Chu on PBS, 1997 Oct 15 (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - Nubel Potratt Kem/FYSIK, 1998 Jan 19 (Box 16, Folder 19)
    - Swedish TV Nobel Tapes, Undated (Box 16, Folder 20)
    - Steven Chu: Nobel Laureate, Undated (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Classes
    - Physics 230 (1 of 3), 2002/2003 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Physics 230 (2 of 3), 2002/2003 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Physics 230 (3 of 3), 2002/2003 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - PSE (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Problem Sets (1 of 2) (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Problem Sets (2 of 2) (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Notebooks
    - Muonium I (1 of 2), 1986 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Muonium I (2 of 2), 1987 Feb 23 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Muonium, 1987 Feb 23 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Muonium II, 1987 May 18 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - DNA Bending, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Nanocrystal, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Physics Lab Notebook, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Bell Labs: GaP:N Vol. I (1 of 2) (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Bell Labs: GaP:N Vol. I (2 of 2) (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Bell Labs: Positronium Expt. (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Bell Labs: Sign-Out Book (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Bell Labs: Anderson Localization Ruby (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Bell Labs: GaP:N Vol. II (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Bell Labs: GaP:N Vol. III (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Bell Labs: Seminars (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Awards (Box 16-18)
    - Nobel Laureate- University of California, 1997 (Box 17)
    - Plaque of Appreciation - Stanford University, 18 Aug 1998 (Box 17)
    - Alliance to Save Energy, 17 Sep 2009 (Box 17)
    - University of Central Floria - School of Optics, 11-12 Jan 1999 (Box 18)
    - Faculty Research, 22 May 2000 (Box 18)
    - Parker H Petit- Distinguished Lecturer, 20 Oct 2006 (Box 18)
    - LINK Americas Foundation - Exemplary Leadership, undated (Box 19)
    - Richard C Lord Lecturer - Massachusetts Institute of Technology, 2001 (Box 19)
    - Hong Kong University of Science and Technology, 6 Aug 2001 (Box 19)
    - University of Rochester - Official Seal, undated (Box 19)
    - American Leadership Forum - Exemplary Leadership, 2001 (Box 20)
    - ACS Green Chemistry Institute - Keynote Speaker, 2008 (Box 20)
    - Hong Kong University of Science and Technology- Distinguished Lecturer in Science, 26 Mar 1998 (Box 20)
    - University of Wisconsin - La Crosse - Distinguished Lecturer in Physics, 26-27 Sep 2001 (Box 21)
    - Sandia/California Distinguished Lecturer, Dec 2005 (Box 21)
    - Institute of Physics- Singapore - Honorary Fellowship, 8 Dec 1998 (Box 21)
    - Case Western Reserve University - Michelson Lecture, 2003 (Box 21)
    - University of Akron- Symposium Lecturer - Waldo Semon Award, 17 Apr 1998 (Box 21)
    - Air Force Office of Scientific Research, 25 Apr 2002 (Box 22)
    - The Optical Society (OSA) - Advocate of Optics, 2013 (Box 22)
    - Chinese Academy of Sciences, undated (Box 22)
    - King Abdulaziz City for Science and Technology, undated (Box 23)
    - Detroit Economic Club (Photograph), 11 Jan 2012 (Box 23)
    - Medal, undated (Box 23)
    - Ministerial meeting between Steven Chu and Sukwoo HONG, 6 Dec 2012 (Box 23)
    - Johns Hopkins - Asian American Heritage Club, 1 June 2012 (Box 23)
    - 9th SCBA International Symposium - Special Appreciation for Outstanding Plenary Lecture, 8 Aug 2001 (Box 24)
    - Harvard Business School Association of Northern California - Business Leader of the Year, 2009 (Box 24)
    - AmVets "Post-109" Americanism Leadership, undated (Box 24)
    - NARUC- Special Thanks, undated (Box 24)
    - International Acheivement Summit, 2002 (Box 25)
    - University of Pennsylvania - Franklin Founder, 20 Jan 2012 (Box 25)
    - Congratulations from Congressman Michael M Honda, 30 Aug 2008 (Box 25)
    - Fudan University - W. Z. Yang Lectureship, 23 Aug 1998 (Box 25)
    - University of Rochester Honorary Degree, 16 May 1998 (Box 25)
    - University of California, Berkeley - Alumnus of the Year, 9 Apr 2011 (Box 25)
    - Realm of the Arctic Circle, 28 Mar 2009 (Box 25)
    - The American Physical Society - Outstanding Referee, 15 Feb 2009 (Box 25)
    - Honorary Director certificate - Shanghai Jiaotong University, undated (Box 25)
    - Honorary Professor - Shanghai Jiaotong University, Jun 2002 (Box 25)
    - Shanghai Institute of Optics and Fine Mechanics - Honorary Professor, 21 Apr 1998 (Box 25)
    - Los Angeles County Sheriff's Department - Certificate of Recognition, 9 Nov 2002 (Box 27)
    - California Legislature Assembly - certificate of recognition, 28 Feb 2004 (Box 27)
    - California State Board of Equalization - Excellence in Science, 9 Nov 2002 (Box 27)
    - County of Los Angeles - Office of the Assessor - certificate of recognition, 9 Nov 2002 (Box 27)
    - California State Assembly - Certificate of Recognition, 9 Nov 2002 (Box 27)
    - California State Assembly - Certificate of Recognition, 9 Nov 2002 (Box 27)
    - California State Assembly - Certificate of Recognition, 9 Nov 2002 (Box 27)
    - City of Los Angeles - certificate of recognition, 9 Nov 2002 (Box 27)
    - County of Los Angeles - commendation, 9 Nov 2002 (Box 27)
    - Nobel Laureate Public Lecture Series Dinner (Photographs), 5 Jul 2005 (Box 27)
    - IOP Institute of Physics - Honorary Fellowship, undated (Box 27)
    - Letter to Dr Chu from Taro Aso - Prime Minister of Japan, 1 May 2009 (Box 27)
- Additional papers, Accession ARCH-2014-012
  - Optical Molasses Data + Graphs, 1988 Jun 5 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Optical Molasses Data + Graphs, 1988 Jun 17 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Optical Molasses Data + Graphs, 1988 Jun 10 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Optical Molasses Data + Graphs, 1988 Jun 8 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Optical Molasses Data + Graphs, 1988 Jun 7 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Optical Molasses Data + Graphs, 1988 Jun 2 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Optical Molasses Data + Graphs, 1988 Jun 4 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Optical Molasses Data + Graphs, 1988 Jun 6 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Optical Molasses Data + Graphs, 1988 Jun 3 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - To max 25 mm probe - various txy, undated (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Curves f.t. to 026As, undated (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Tz Max with 50 cm/5vd, undated (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - vp +11mm with Txy Down - 17 mm, undated (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - NIIA - fitted curves, undated (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - TOF Charted Max Imo - 17 mm + 8mm +11m, undated (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - computer program printouts, undated (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Horizontal probe TOF, undated (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Optical Molasses Data + Graphs, 1988 May 11 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Optical Molasses Data + Graphs, 1988 May 12 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Optical Molasses Data + Graphs, 1988 May 17 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Optical Molasses Data + Graphs, 1988 May 19 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Optical Molasses Data + Graphs, 1988 May 20 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Optical Molasses Data + Graphs, 1988 May 23 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Optical Molasses Data + Graphs, 1988 May 25 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Optical Molasses Data + Graphs, 1988 May 27 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Optical Molasses Data + Graphs, 1988 May 30 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Optical Molasses Data + Graphs, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Graphs + Data, 1988 Aug 30 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Graphs + Data, 1988 Oct 12 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Graphs + Data, 1988 Oct 13 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Graphs + Data, 1988 Oct 14-15 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Graphs + Data, 1988 Oct 17 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Graphs + Data, 1988 Oct 19 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Graphs + Data, 1988 Oct 20 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Graphs + Data, 1988 Oct 21 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Graphs + Data, 1988 Oct 26 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Graphs + Data, 1988 Oct 27-28 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Graphs + Data, 1988 Nov 8 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Graphs + Data, 1988 Nov 11 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Graphs + Data, 1988 Nov 12 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Data + Graphs, 1988 Jun 15 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Graphs + Data, 1988 Jul 27-28 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Graphs + Data, 1988 Jul 29-Aug 1 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Graphs + Data, 1988 Aug 2 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Graphs + Data, 1988 Aug 10 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Graphs + Data, 1988 Aug 12 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Graphs + Data, 1988 Aug 15 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Graphs + Data, 1988 Aug 17 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Graphs + Data, 1988 Aug 18 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Graphs + Data, 1988 Aug 22 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Graphs + Data, 1988 Aug 19 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Graphs + Data, 1988 Aug 23 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Graphs + Data, 1988 Aug 26 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Graphs + Data, 1988 Aug 27 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Graphs + Data, 1988 Aug 30 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Graphs + Data, 1988 Sep 1 (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Optical Molasses Data + Graphs, 1988 Nov 16-25 (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Optical Molasses Data + Graphs, 1988 Nov 26-28 (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - Optical Molasses Data + Graphs, 1988 Nov 30 (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - Optical Molasses Data + Graphs, 1988 Dec 1 (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - Optical Molasses Data + Graphs, 1988 Dec 3 (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - Optical Molasses Data + Graphs, 1988 Dec 5 (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - Optical Molasses Data + Graphs, 1988 Dec 6 (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - Optical Molasses Data + Graphs, 1988 Dec 7 (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - Optical Molasses Data + Graphs, 1988 Dec 8 (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - Davi Weiss' Personal Notebook - Chu Group: Vol II - Optical Moldsses Multilevel Atoms, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - Davi Weiss' Personal Notebook - Chu Group: Vol II - Optical Moldsses Multilevel Atoms, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 67)
  - Davi Weiss' Personal Notebook - Chu Group: Vol II - Optical Moldsses Multilevel Atoms, 1987 Oct-1988 Apr (Box 1, Folder 68)
  - Data Fit, 1988 Dec (Box 1, Folder 69)
  - Optical Molasses Data + Graphs, 1989 Jan 7-10 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Optical Molasses Data + Graphs, 1989 Jan 12 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Optical Molasses Data + Graphs, 1989 Jan 13 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Optical Molasses Data + Graphs, 1989 Jan 14 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Data + Graphs, 1989 Feb 13 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Data + Graphs, 1989 Feb 15 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Data + Graphs, 1989 Feb 16 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Data + Graphs, 1989 Feb 17 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Data + Graphs, 1989 Feb 17 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Data + Graphs, 1989 Feb 23 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Data + Graphs, 1989 Feb 24 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - (Not labeled) Data + Graphs, 1989 Feb 25 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Data + Graphs, 1989 Feb 27 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Graphs + Data, 1989 Apr 19 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Data + Graphs, 1989 May 10 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Data + Graphs, 1989 May 12 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Data + Graphs, 1989 May 17 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Data + Graphs, 1989 May 19 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Data + Graphs, 1989 May 26 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Funnel Characterization Graphs + Data =- Loose Papers, 1989 Nov (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Optical Molasses Data + Graphs, May 2-May 4 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - David Weiss' Personal Notebook- Atomic Funnel - Chu. Inc, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Temp (sidebond tren + interity Linear lines), 1989 Mar 1 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Data + Graphs, 1989 Mar 1 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Data + Graphs, 1989 Mar 2 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Data + Graphs, 1989 Mar 3 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Data + Graphs, 1989 Mar 6 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Data + Graphs, 1989 Mar 9 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - ID Equilibration: Linear-Linear-Low Intensity + 2 Level, 1989 Feb 25 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - ID Equilibration: Linear-Linear-Corkscrew Pul., 1989 Feb 25 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - ID Equilibration: Crossed Linear (probe set to 1 minz), 1989 Feb 25 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - ID Equilbration: Crosse Linear (had high time blogs), 1989 Mar 1 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - ID Equilibration: Linear-Linera, 1989 Feb 25 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - ID Equilibration: Two-level, 1989 Feb 2 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Data + Graphs for various topics (loose in the box, clipped together), 1989 Mar 1 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Data + Graphs, 1994 Apr 6-7 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Data + Graphs for Ex__Dat, undated (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Fits: I.D. Equilibrium, I=155, 35 m, 1989 May 10 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Graphs + Data of various topics (I.D.Equili. included), 1989 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Calculations, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Temp. Frequency, 1989 Mar 14 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Extra Figures and Diagonal State Data, 1989 Apr 15 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Graphs + Data, 1989 Jun 7 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Graphs + Data, 1989 Jun 5 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Graphs + Data, 1989 Jun 9 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Graphs + Data of various topics (I.D.Equili. included), 1989 Jun 10 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Data + Graphs, 1989 Jun 12 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Graphs + Data, 1989 Jun 13 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - 5" Floppy Disks, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Data + Graph, 1989 Aug 15 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Data + Graphs, 1989 Oct 3 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Data + Graphs, 1989 Oct 4 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Graphs + Data, 1989 Oct 5 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Data + Graphs, 1989 Nov 4 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Graphs + Data, 1989 Nov 6 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Graphs + Data, 1989 Nov 8 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Graphs + Data, 1989 Nov 9 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Graphs + Data, 1989 Nov 11 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Graphs + Data - Funnel Characterization, 1989 Nov 25 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Graphs + Data - Funnel Characterization, 1989 Nov 27 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Graphs + Data - Funnel Characterization, 1989 Nov 29 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - N30 Data Analysis, 1989 Nov 30 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - A, B Scans - Analyzing (graphs included), 1989 Dec 2 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Transverse Temp. Analysis, Dec (year unknown) (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Graphs + Data using Blaster Pulse, 1989 Nov 20 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Graphs + Data After Blaster Pulse was used, 1989 Nov 22 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Eliminate Interference in Raman Beam by Inperfect Retroreflection, 1992 Oct 22-25 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Switch to Blackman Pulses for pi/2's, 1992 Oct 28 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Eliminate Interference in Raman Beams by Titling Pinhole + Using Coupling Gel, 1992 Nov 2-8 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Change PMT Imaging: 1) Replace Interference Filter w/ Longpass Filter 2) Add 2nd Lens, 1992 Nov 21-Dec 12 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Check for Dependence on Standing Waves in the Raman Beams, 1993 Jan 6-16 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Working w/o Standing Waves (o+, o-), 1993 Jan 20 - Feb 15 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - C(s) Beam Flux, undated (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Raman Beam Profile, undated (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Phase - Lock Jitter, 1992 Nov 7 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Vibration Measures, 1993 Jan 21 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Graphs + Data, 1989 Jun 1 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Graph, 1989 Jun 8 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Graphs + Data, 1989 Jun 2 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Graphs + Data, 1991 Jun 22 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Graphs + Data, 1991 Jun 25 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Graphs, 1991 Jul 1 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Graphs + Data, 1991 Jul 2 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Graphs + Data, 1991 Jul 3 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Graphs + Data, 1991 Jul 5 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Graphs + Data, 1991 Jul 26 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Graphs + Data, 1991 Aug 5 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Graphs + Data, 1991 Aug 23 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Graphs + Data, 1991 Aug 24 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Graphs + Data, 1991 Aug 26 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Graphs + Data, 1991 Aug 27 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Graphs + Data, 1991 Aug 28 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Graphs + Data, 1991 Sep 10 (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Graphs + Data, 1991 Sep 11 (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - Graph + Data, 1991 Sep 12 (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - Graphs + Data, 1991 Sep 13 (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - Graphs + Data, 1991 Sep 19 (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - Graphs + Data, 1991 Sep 20 (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - Graphs + Data, 1991 Sep 26 (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - Graphs + Data, 1991 Sep 28 (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - Graphs + Data, 1991 Oct 30 (Box 3, Folder 53)
  - Graphs + Data, 1991 Oct 31 (Box 3, Folder 54)
  - Graphs + Data, 1991 Nov 1 (Box 3, Folder 55)
  - Longitudinal Temp. Analysis, undated (Box 3, Folder 56)
  - Magnetic Field of Hose, undated (Box 3, Folder 57)
  - More Temp. Analysis, Dec 15 and on (Box 3, Folder 58)
  - B-Field & RF Sidebonds, undated (Box 3, Folder 59)
  - More Calculations - Mostly Chemical, undated (Box 3, Folder 60)
  - Program PLOTF, undated (Box 3, Folder 61)
  - Commencement speeches, 1999-2013; 10 computer file(s) (pdf)
  - Duke University - Certificate of Recognition, 14 May 2006 (Box 26)
  - New Jersey Inventors Hall of Fame - Trustees Award, 2012 (Box 26)
  - China Association for Science and Technology, undated (Box 26)
  - McGraw-Hill Encylopedia of Physics (Photo), undated (Box 26)
  - untitled, unframed photo, undated (Box 26)
  - framed, untitled photo, undated (Box 26)
  - Linus Pauling Medal, 2003-2004 (Box 26)
  - Chinese Academy of Science (Photo), undated (Box 28)
  - Environmental Law Institute - Annual Award, 19 Oct 2011 (Box 29)
  - Framed photo, undated (Box 30)
- Additional papers, Accession ARCH-2018-074
  - Cartoon of Chu with Tennis Racket (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Awards, certificates, honorary doctorates, photographs (Box 1, Folder 2-5)
  - Plaque of Appreciation - Hallim Distinguished Lecture, The Korean Academy of Science and Technology, 1998 Aug 17 (Box 2)
  - Steven Chu, Nobel Laureate - University Lecture Series in Chemistry, Boston College, 2000 Feb 9-11 (Box 3)
  - Framed painting of Chinese symbol (Box 4)